{
    "id": "3dec8f7d81ab42d78912e78d42a0e999",
    "title": "Time Expressions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ..................................... breakfast at 8 am every day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8f5ec5185e654882be8f08a1fdffc96d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................................... breakfast at 8 am yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a9eca1b6a9d548ef87fcb012e6700498"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog ........................................ all night yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is barking",
                "was barking",
                "has been barking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0817fa75db7547579dd452eebaffb184"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog .................................... at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "barks",
                "is barking",
                "barked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b3856a37085344a093f2d0b0afa1ede9"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog ................................... for hours last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was barking",
                "has barked",
                "barked"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2057d011354643a0af0b3df7894d121b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .......................................... the newspaper every morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "have read",
                "was reading"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1143fd0b883d4d7d87c212ef3520a9dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................................... the newspaper at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "am reading",
                "was reading"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2aa07994db1d4b9da844ca575ac2ea1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ................................... me English for three hours last Sunday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taught",
                "is teaching",
                "has taught"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a09cd1d82ecf48b582fd6b06f9b24d3b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ................................... me English at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "teaches",
                "is teaching",
                "taught"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2bb6f42e47c0404f92e029375499da8a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ..................................... me English every day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "teaches",
                "is teaching",
                "has taught"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4cd7d5e359174b47a366425dee78c78f"
        }
    ]
}